And it might help a little bit.
I'm now in my hotspot, is that better?
Yeah, marginally.
Let me turn the video off.
I could, I could, I could,
I could at least hear you.
Okay, how are we now? Is this better?
Yes, I can hear you.
Okay, okay, let's go. Good morning,
how are you?
No.
Yeah, very good in you.
I'm good.
If you turn your videos off as well,
maybe that's even better.
I have.
Yeah, okay, good.
I still see a picture of you.
Yeah.
Okay.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
We've been very hectic,
but now I can concentrate.
So why don't we?
No, fair enough. I can understand that,
but...
So, I sent you a message this morning.
Hello, yeah, yes, yeah, I saw that.
And we obviously do this all the time.
And these are like what impresses people.
So if I can say you can make an HR
chatbot and I show an HR chatbot,
they say, yeah, that's fine,
but I want to see it for us.
And if I would literally have five or six
documents,
and different documents and differently
formatted documents, you know,
no consistency in that.
Then I just literally on stage in 5
minutes create a chat bot that costs you
nothing to run in your organisation that
people can interact with.
And then I think it starts to
dawn on people that you don't need an
external consulting firm and big
technology to make AI work in your
company. Does that make sense?
Yes, yeah, no, 100%.
The other thing that we do, Jacob.
I actually fiddled a little bit with the
chatbot towards the end of last year with
regards to some stuff that we do,
but I was using more websites,
our website to produce data,
which I found quite worked quite well.
But yeah, no, I agree.
I think that would work.
I have started getting some documents
together.
They're currently in the SharePoint
library,
so I'm just downloading them and then I
will forward them through to you a little
later.
Yeah,
I think that's very powerful because
instead then people having to go in a
SharePoint, they can see that.
Yes.
The other thing that we do is very
quickly create a labour law advisor on
the basis of the Labour Relations Act,
conditions of employment and the other
act. And then basically say, look,
Anyone in the organisation that has a
question how to deal with a situation
like sexual harassment or when, you know,
when are people entitled to certain
things? Again,
I can show creating that in 5 minutes.
And then everyone that manages people can
ask questions so that your organisation
stays in compliance
with labour law. That's also like,
you see, that's also something.
Maybe we are.
And I show these things like 5 minutes,
5 minutes, 5 minutes.
What if your entire organization,
everyone could start to capture knowledge
and make it easily accessible?
The other thing that I'd like to show is
Yeah.
a contract that you've entered into that
you've paid a lot of money to
external legal advisors for.
We generally don't use legal advisors.
We tend to do it ourselves internally.
But I have managed to,
we did one towards the end of last year.
That was a backwards, back and forth,
back and forth.
And there were quite a lot of changes to
it eventually.
So I'll get that out. I just,
what I'll do is I'll forward you NDA just
to obviously sign that off.
Because obviously it is a supply
Yeah, of course, Anna. Yeah, yeah,
absolutely.
agreement with one of our customers. But
You can take all of that out if you wish.
That's the other thing that we could do.
Uh, that's too much,
too much like hard work.
Yeah, yeah, understood, understood.
The reason why I lost the begin...
Botha.
And on the basis that we want to
obviously do the training and all the
other bits, I think India might just be,
make everyone comfortable and then we can.
Absolutely.
Get information freely, yeah.
Because what I want to show is that
here's a contract.
You can do an immediate review.
But what lawyers never do,
and we had to discuss you with three
lawyers in the masterclass this week.
They say, we always say to a client,
start with the most tough contract.
I'm like,
that only serves your purpose because now
you're wasting a lot of
hours because at the end you have a
watered down contract.
Why not at the beginning say to the model,
this contract is very important for us
because it's a big custom in a new
industry that we want to enter.
So maybe we want to give in a little bit
because it's more important for us to
lend the client.
than to have a strong contract that's in
our favor.
So now you do two things at the same time.
You look at the legality,
you look at what is in your commercial
interest.
And then the third thing that we show is
that it already writes the e-mail to
negotiate certain points away.
So let's say you look at a contract,
there's 10 points of contention.
The 2 ones are non-negotiables.
The top five one you can easily give up
in line of the commercial interest and
the other ones are for negotiation.
So we basically create the list and then
say,
if we start to give in on what's easy to
give up, we start to say, okay,
we see a point, we see a point,
we see a point. And the last
at the end of the e-mail, you say,
these points,
we'd like to stay as they are.
Then you see that that particular e-mail
may lead to the opposing legal advisor to
say, you know,
it's actually quite reasonable,
contract done.
Yeah.
And that goes in a different direction
than how a lawyer is taught
to think about negotiations.
And then what hopefully happens is that
from contract version number one to the
contract that you ultimately signed,
it's a much better process. And secondly,
there's a lot more intelligence that went
into the contract review.
And also you can do more of that yourself.
Sure.
So you start to give agency to more
managers in the organisation as to how to
deal with information.
We want to show all of these tricks so
that your team says, damn,
we need to go and do this masterclass
Eat.
because we can do a lot of the work
ourselves.
Yes.
And that's why I know which case studies
people like.
No, for sure, definitely.
And the last one,
do you have a project for a new line of
business that you were thinking about?
Nothing at the moment.
We've, yeah,
we've just towards the end of last year,
we got managed it, but I mean,
on that basis,
and that was also why I suggested when we
talk. So,
the one thing we identified last year,
Remy heads up our innovations, our R&
Yes.
D department.
Yes.
So what happens is they deal a lot with
what we call industrial customers.
So big customers that obviously have what
they call travelling ovens and stuff like
Yes.
Yeah.
that.
And him and his team would go on site to
Okay.
the customer.
There'd be obviously a lot of interaction,
talking about things,
discussing things with the customers,
obviously saying this is what they want.
They want softer bread.
but with a crust, top hard crust,
et cetera, et cetera.
And they obviously take pictures,
they take samples, all that kind of stuff.
And generally what they do when they get
back to the office,
they obviously have to try and listen to
what you can see in their notes.
They have tried to record some of them on
the odd occasion.
and then draught a report back to the
customer and obviously then come up with
ideas.
So what we were looking at trying to do,
and we did get a quote,
we just haven't taken it further.
And I thought, well, you know,
possibly we might be able to do it
ourselves after doing masterclass. But so.
Essentially, we're looking to say, well,
when they're on site, take the pictures,
take the recordings of the discussion,
insert the notes, etc.,
generate a report for the customer,
as well as taking that data and...
starting to produce our own LLM so that
we can then put a bot against it to start,
once we obviously get some history,
to be able to go, okay, well,
I got a guy that's got claps in bread.
Yeah,
who else has had it and how did we
resolve the topic?
Excellent. So I'll do something like that,
not for your business, but you know what?
Once you use the platforms, you know,
Claude, Chat T or Gemini,
Yes.
you don't need to get additional stuff
and you must certainly not ask.
someone to build a system.
Just to give you an idea,
and I want to show that because I did it
yesterday night.
So one CEO of an industrial organisation
said something silly.
I want to have an agent that runs around
in my e-mail system to pick up any issues
between my customers and my sales
managers.
And he said, I want the agent to do this.
So I costed it for him. And I said,
it's going to cost you a million rand.
But if people run this prompt themselves
every morning at 7 o'clock,
They can do it for free.
Here's the prompt.
I can't be bothered to have any further
discussion.
I don't think you should spend a million
rand. You don't have to pay me.
Here's the prompt.
Okay, sounds good.
And this is what I wonder,
what did they quote you that system for,
may I ask?
It was came in just, well,
initial development was 200,000.
You know what? No, don't do that.
Going forward,
one of my philosophies that I will share
with your team is that I think
organisations will start to look like
black stars.
All kinds of functions like legal and
procurement and HR will implode in
themselves because managers that are at
actually doing business,
start to do a lot more themselves.
So, yeah.
The same goes for your IT team.
Instead of your IT team going out to
external parties to create custom-made
systems,
you can make custom-made systems yourself.
So as part of the master class,
after two days,
the people in the master class
create vibe-coded apps for their business.
That's the purpose.
So once people have seen that they can
take an idea to a working web app in
about 20 minutes,
that's when everyone says,
now I get it why we need to do AI.
Because we can build software.
Yeah.
We call it disposable software.
You can even build software for
just one project, because it can be done,
it's cheap. So yesterday,
or the day before yesterday,
one of the participants was late and I
said, no, AI works like your brain.
He said, that's ********.
But I knew he was an anesthesiologist and
that he knows about brain. So I'm like,
okay, let me be careful here.
He was very skeptical. He,
yesterday afternoon, anesthesiologist,
he built a copy of the Viva app.
I don't know if you know the Viva app.
That's the one that runs on your phone
and then you scan a wine bottle,
gives you the price, the rating,
and what you should eat and drink.
Yes, yeah.
He built it in 5 minutes.
Then I helped him add the camera
capability.
And make it work on iOS, Mac, Android,
and a PC.
And this guy is like,
I cannot believe what I just did. I said,
see how easy it is?
So I'd love to show you an idea whereby
you work with a customer.
Let's say they send you spec,
you record the interview,
you take a couple of pictures,
and then how very quickly you turn that
into a product description, a proposal.
etc.
So that hopefully your team instead of...
Yep, sounds good.
So these are the things I want to show on
Monday.
It's not a consulting presentation.
We're not talking about the 4th
Industrial Revolution and how the world
will change. We just say,
here's a couple of applications.
Once you see...
Couple of things to whet the appetite to
take the next step.
Yes. Well, also to say,
this is what you can do.
I like.
This is what you can do. And, you know,
this is not theory. This is practice.
Who is?
The other thing that we,
so in addition to organisations becoming
black holes that implode in themselves,
we say your organisation will start to
look like a pancake.
The people that want to do this,
They're going to do a hell of a lot more.
And it could be young people that are
lower in the chain that adopt this
technology. It could be older people.
But you know what, if you embrace AI,
you're going to do a lot more.
You're going to be successful.
If you resist AI, unfortunately,
in the future,
there will be no job for you.
I'm not talking about the shop floor,
obviously, but in
the people with brains.
We talk a little bit philosophy,
Sure.
Yes, Marshall.
but it's like all positive. It's like,
guys, let's do this.
And the outcome of the masterclasses,
I had my first meeting this morning at 6.
30 that originated yesterday out of the
masterclass. Lots of people said, okay,
we're going to do this now.
They're getting enthusiastic.
By the way,
do you know what the average age of the
masterclass participants has been for the
last two months? What do you think?
I have.
That's a tough one. I,
my gut's sort of telling me that, well,
the head sang probably in the 30s,
my gut sang probably more forty-five 50.
5560.
Sure, OK.
All people that say, when they,
because we do, you know,
how do you feel about AI? They say,
I'm a complete novice.
I don't know anything. I said,
the fact that you're sitting here making
this investment means that you're ahead
of everyone else.
Nel, yeah.
And walking out after two days says, yeah,
we now are ahead of the young people in
our organization.
They never talk about this and they can't
do this. And I have to
Teach them.
And that's the magic. And the other thing,
my first slide is why AI?
Because it's fun. It's fun.
your work becomes fun again.
And it will lead to cost savings,
Yeah.
more revenue optimization.
But the first thing is fun.
That's what we pick up.
People walk out of the two days,
they're getting young again.
They're like smiling, they're excited,
etc. Now let's talk about your system.
So I'm happy that you're in agreement
with
with kind of what we want to show.
Then the first hour I make sure I touch
Yeah.
everything. I show what I want to show,
which I think is good for your team to
know. Then the additional time I say, hey,
if you want to just ask me a question,
can you do this? Can you do that?
so that if they have more questions or
they want to test me on the spot or they
want to see something live coded on the
screen,
that we do that because that's then
additionally impressive. You know,
this is on the spot.
So one of the things that I did yesterday,
Yes.
so we have a hypothetical case study
about a whiskey investment business.
So like,
I don't know if you know Whiskey Brother.
that chain of whiskey bars where you can
invest in whiskey.
Klara.
And so I give it a small one-pager,
this is the business,
and then I say to Excel using Claude,
create a financial model of it,
including the assumptions, the scenarios,
the revenues, the cost, and the cash flow,
because I'm not interested in the balance
sheet and income statement, because
trying to decide whether we should invest
in this business and throw the cash in it.
Yeah.
So then in five, 10 minutes,
he makes a spreadsheet.
Then I go into the spreadsheet because
Whiskey Brothers is based on retail sites
with retail rents. And then I say, okay,
this is an average of the retail cost
across the country.
But now give me the retail
for Cape Town or within Cape Town,
Claremont. And then it live goes online,
finds the retail rates on average for
Claremont.
And then I update the spreadsheet to see
what impact that has on the on the on the
bottom line.
And that's not scenarios like you know,
high, low.
or middle, this is like,
let's throw in real time costs.
Then I show what is the average salary of
the workers that you want in there.
Tom.
Let's throw that in. Then I say, okay,
I need a sales manager.
Let's create a profile of the sales
manager.
So now it creates a profile in Excel.
My spreadsheet is doing all this work now.
Then I say,
I've got a profile of a salesperson.
Now go online and find me a candidate.
So now it gives you literally next to
your spreadsheet 5 candidates.
In the meantime,
I asked it the property that I was most
interested in, find me the realtor,
their mobile phone number and their
e-mail address. Write them an e-mail.
telling them I'm interested in this
property and explain my business and what
my needs are and then send it to them.
And it's all happening in a spreadsheet.
It looks chaotic, but then people say,
Verushca.
what the hell? Did you just do that?
You replaced my HR department.
You replaced our external recruiting
agent.
You replaced my property manager from
within a spreadsheet. They say, yeah,
after two days in a masterclass,
you can do that.
Unfortunately, not with Copilot.
That much I know.
This.
You see,
that was one of the reasons why I moved
on from the business that I set up years
ago is I was in a Microsoft distributor
and like it doesn't work.
It doesn't work and I think you are,
you have a big Microsoft estate, right?
Yeah.
Big Microsoft.
But you can run Claude from within
Microsoft. By the way,
Claude is now being licenced to Microsoft
so that they can once and for all fix
Excel with AI.
Okay, cool.
So Microsoft is buying Claude's
technology. So we can say, look,
we don't tell you to switch platforms at
all. I run Microsoft myself.
I can show that within Microsoft,
I run OpenAI, Claude, Gemini and Grok.
Those are the four systems that we work
with.
Okay.
So that's the two hours.
So we can finish after an hour,
but if people want to talk more,
I'm ready to show more engaging examples
Yeah.
if they want to, but we don't have to.
No, I think that,
I think that makes perfect sense,
because obviously, yeah, you get the,
you've started,
you've shown them some options,
and obviously, while doing that,
people probably get prompted,
and then yeah,
I think the second hour for them to ask
questions or get some more detail would
be would be good.
Yeah. And then we say to people, you know,
how do you get started?
Because often people want to start,
you know, what if AI could fix the world?
We say, that's not how we start.
Start small, get everyone excited,
have quick wins,
and then fix the big problems later.
Because once everyone knows how AI work
and then master it themselves,
you might find that a lot of people in
the organisation can start to contribute
to the solution, the building parts of it.
Again, a bit philosophical,
but we see it happening in real life.
Why don't you tell me what your system is
and where we can tap into,
or not so much tap into, but you said,
I want to explain our system to you.
That's interesting.
Well, yeah,
so it's just obviously from a business
point of view,
and it's probably more sort of our
organisational structure,
business structure.
So we have a manufacturing plant in Jacob.
OK.
where we manufacture bakery premixes.
And from there,
OK.
we ship product around the country to
what we call our branches,
for want of a better word,
probably distribution centers.
Okay.
But they also buy our product.
So we've obviously got in all the major
cities.
centers.
We pretty much use SysPro as our ELP.
Hey, yeah.
We do make use of a product data scope,
WMS and right scan for scanning
capabilities within our warehouse
operations.
And then pretty much obviously everything
else runs through Microsoft.
OK.
Obviously we do that quite a bit.
From the...
IT side, as I explained,
Martin looks after IT for BidCorp and we
have a shared services for the technical
side.
So that's where his involvement comes.
And then I look after a small team of
four that obviously does the systems team.
Yeah, we obviously do,
we've tied in with a couple of suppliers,
not necessarily tied in,
but we've got a small list of suppliers
that we procure from.
We do procure quite a bit from overseas.
We're a joint venture with for artists in
Belgium.
So we do have quite a bit of product that
comes in from them.
Yeah, of course.
I need.
I know them.
I'm from the south of Holland.
I grew up 10 minutes from the Belgian
border.
Okay, cool.
And you can see, yeah.
Um, yeah, no, so yeah, it was more just...
Yeah,
that was probably more just to sort of
explain,
give a bit of background about our
business.
I don't know if you've got any specific
questions.
And then obviously the other thing was to
try and explain the issue with Remy,
which we've obviously discussed now.
And I think showing him something on that
will make him very excited.
Thanks.
Yeah, so I'll focus on that. Definitely,
that's a good insight. Look,
I always try and stay away from, you know,
integration with your systems for two
reasons.
I'm not one of those consultants that
sells anything and then tries to look
smart. I just say, look,
I haven't looked at your system.
I don't know.
I'm not going to pretend to know.
No, sure.
business.
Although I know I worked with the people
that make Wonder Bread and the other
stuff that lasts on the shelf for 200
days and never goes off.
So I had to look into the bread industry
The.
Okay.
Yeah.
in this country. But I tried to say, look,
guys, let's start working together.
Let's do this together.
I'm an expert in AI, but
I'm not an expert in your business and
I'm never going to pretend to be one.
So sometimes I can't answer yet how the
integration works with your system.
Now on your system,
are you very much driven by what your
T.
holding company tells you to use?
No, well, they probably want us to be.
We're not.
I know at the moment between Belgium and
South Africa, they're both sort of going,
well, if you're going to use AI, co-pilot.
But I mean,
we want to see all the staff are pretty
much using,
OK.
a lot of them are using ChatGPT.
But again,
it's something that we've obviously got
to assess and discuss, and if we need to,
we'd take it up and address it with.
Then the main thing obviously is around
the knowledge base and sharing of
information,
because obviously we understand when
we've got a customer and develop a bread
premix for them. For instance,
we do work for Albany,
that's obviously very much restricted and
Yes.
we obviously...
can't be,
can't put at risk the formulations
getting out into the market, etc.
So that's more,
that was more the reason I think behind
doing co-pilot is that they can ring
fence it with regards to information
sharing.
No, they can't.
And that's why in that instance,
I would say buy an Nvidia box for 120,
000 Rand and run a model locally.
So that's something I will want to show
as well,
that for these types of applications,
you run a model on your own hardware
disconnected from the internet.
No.
Okay.
The reason I'm telling you is because I
used to run and still run a military
grade cyber defence company.
So I'm going to tell you, look,
whatever you put in ChatGPT or co-pilot
or Gemini or Grok meets the same level of
security, which is very high.
It meets the same level of privacy.
It's very high.
I also need to explain to people that a
large language model is not a database in
the traditional sense that if you upload
a PDF document,
Sh.
you can go and look for it.
It doesn't get stored in a large language
model.
So even if people have access to the
large language model,
they would never ever be able to find the
recipe in the large language model.
But where you lose,
where you could lose that Albany recipe
is in the interaction, you know,
when people start to send each other
emails and in the chat interface, etc. So,
but I'll address cybersecurity, privacy,
Poppy as well,
and then take the concern away.
because Co-Pilot runs on the same
infrastructure and the same Azure as
OpenAI.
And I can show you a side-by-side
comparison of privacy and security
measures from both OpenAI and Co-Pilot.
I don't know if you agree or disagree or
have questions on that.
No, no, no, agreed.
I think that's definitely,
that is obviously one of the,
and I'm sure if it's not raised,
it'll be one of the questions that gets
asked. So it's probably good to cover it.
Yeah, and I had to,
because I still work a lot with Discovery
Bank and Discovery Group.
So that came up 2 1/2 years ago.
So I had to look at it,
into it for them 2 1/2 years ago,
and it comes up all the time.
So every company we work with,
every masterclass,
but my legal tells me we cannot attach a
document to ChatGPT or Co-Pilot or Gemini.
OK.
This is what happens with the information.
If you're happy to put it on your
OneDrive,
if you're happy to e-mail it unencrypted,
even to the Albany people,
I can guarantee you that the e-mail
exchanges are done.
Unencrypted, is that correct?
Yeah, the emails are done unencrypted.
The recipe is generally,
we don't actually share our recipe with
them.
Okay, are you done? Okay.
It's skipped locally and we just supply
them a final product.
But internally you send e-mail, right?
Yeah, well,
the innovations department don't,
and Remy would be able to explain it
better,
but from my understanding that I put it
into emails, and if they do,
it's attached in an Excel that is
password protected.
Yeah, I can break that in 5 seconds,
so that's not not that.
Yeah, not you, you and me, Botha.
So look, I'm not going to bring that up.
The point is that I will bring up that
even though I think it's secure in that
instance, I would say, for example,
a Mac Studio with 512 gigabytes memory,
not hard drive,
520 gigabytes of unified memory.
Yes, it's going to cost you $10,000.
But for your R&D department,
if they can run the largest large
language models on that box,
unconnected from the internet,
that's super, super safe.
Yes.
So, that's so security we addressed.
What else? Yeah, the one thing,
Okay.
who is your systems integrator that you
work with?
We use Helen from Data Smith.
Okay, okay,
and has he has he bet certain solutions
Is.
to you?
No,
we generally have to ask when we want
stuff.
So we use our sales reps use a product
called Skynema.
Okay.
for their daily calls and they can take
orders.
Okay.
Those orders get pushed back into SYSPRO
with regards, yeah,
Okay.
so they do a direct push back.
And then we also, the retailers,
two of the retailers use a company called
FMCGX.
Okay.
FMCGX gets the orders in,
they ship us those orders,
which Ellen then picks up and then feeds
that into our ERP system by order,
obviously validating prices,
customer accounts, et cetera,
and then those get pulled in.
That's probably, yeah,
Yeah.
that's the main integration.
that we do.
We do make use of another product called
Export Docs,
which is actually in the process of
moving to what they call cross-border.
So that essentially takes our info from
SYSPRO and generates documents for
cross-border permits.
SID 500 forms, those kind of things.
Okay.
That's, yeah,
that's probably the main integrations
that we make use of.
I remember you saying that, yes.
Wish you, yes.
The other thing that I would be
uncomfortable answering at this stage was
someone says,
this is the system that you use,
can you do the following? Like,
I don't know the system.
But also what I want people to understand
that increasingly,
you should start to think about what is
the value of external intelligence versus
my internal data set.
Just to give you an idea,
and we do it in the master class.
And I also talked to it.
So one of the things I knew in my
business, I set up Core Group,
the Apple distributors in this country.
And when in Cape Town,
the ships land with all the tourists,
and the exchange rate has moved in South
African in 15 to 20,
the Europeans and the Americans walk into
the V&
A waterfront and start buying Apple
computers because they are a lot cheaper
than Europe,
because of the adverse movement of the
exchange rate.
Sandra, yeah.
And for years,
I've been trying to tell my IT team and
my finance team that if they start
monitoring movements and cruise ships in
relationship to the exchange rate,
they will have a much better forecasting
tool than looking at historical sellout
data, because if we were out of stock,
they don't capture what they missed
selling.
See, now you get my point.
Stock outs never captured in an ERP
Yes, yeah.
system. So I think that with AI,
we're much better off creating
intelligence from outside data sources
that in the past could not end up in
SysPro. SysPro, for example,
if I sell ice creams on the beach,
SysPro does not capture temperatures.
Cisco doesn't
capture if there was a rugby game in use,
because if it was cold or there was a
rugby game in use,
people don't go to the beach. You see,
Yes, yeah.
that's intelligence. So I say to people,
let's rather look at things that you
don't capture today that give you much
better forecasting power than trying to
integrate your ERP system with your sales
order system,
because then we're going to spend a lot
of money and everyone's getting
frustrated and we're not seeing the
benefit of AI.
Benefits, yeah.
Another thing I want to show, for example,
lots of company, not you,
because you're not in retail or customer
facing,
but lots of people pay a lot of money on
social media monitoring.
and they have an agency and they pay for
a system,
I can show you that if you run a little
agent in on Twitter with Grok that
doesn't cost you more than $30 a month,
you can basically see how people are
complaining about your product or how
they're raving about your product.
Just.
So I don't need an external 50,
000 men a month agency anymore.
I only pay $30 a month.
Yeah, well, yeah, so on saying that,
we do make use of an agency, crap,
You see?
I can't remember their name now,
but we pay them a monthly retainer to
manage and control,
I think it's Facebook and Instagram.
Yes.
for us and our website so that these
three elements that they do.
And they do that on, they just populate,
they put out messages or are they looking
Yeah. No,
I think they just populate and put our
for people?
messages. There's no,
I don't think there's any,
I.
I could be very wrong.
I don't obviously integrate too much on
that side of it. All I know is we do pay.
Not a huge amount of money,
but we do pay them.
Well, in your world, what's not huge?
What's not a huge amount of money, 10,000,
A monthly returner.
20?
Well, yeah, no,
we're probably paying them,
I think we're paying them about 25, 30,
000 now a month.
That's good to know,
because then I can show a couple of
things. How,
let's say you're the marketing person and
you see something on a website that
pertains to your industry,
then you can very quickly say,
tweet about it and say this.
And then you literally can see AI taking
over your browser, your Twitter account,
and
and putting the post out. Obviously,
then your marketing lady will come up in
arms and everyone else will say,
but we have policies and it needs to go
past the marketing committee. He's like,
you know what,
we're paying you one and a half million
Rand a month to actually outsource your
work to a 25,000 Rand a month agency.
Isn't it time we're paying $200 for a
Two.
smart agent that actually does it all?
Yeah, I agree.
I hope she's not. This is how I talk,
Carl, by the way. This is how I talk.
No, no, 100%. I love it. Love it.
You know,
is I tell people I have to pay penance
Yeah.
for the fact that for 25 years,
I've been in the IT industry,
selling expensive systems that no one
knows how to use and they're actually not
that effective.
So thank God we have AI and we can do it
ourselves for a little bit of money.
Botha.
Are there people in the group that are
skeptical, that may push back,
that may have said it doesn't work?
I don't think so.
I think generally we're all quite keen,
and I think it's more around,
like you've explained, practical examples.
So where can we use it? Yeah,
and that's always been part of the
Okay.
challenge. I mean, when you mentioned...
Hello?
Think I lost you.
Hello?
Are you currently muted?
I said I my my my laptop died,
so now I'm on my phone. I'm backwards,
Oh, okay. Yeah,
I was busy talking about all this and
I'm backwards.
just disappeared. Okay. But so I think,
as I said,
we did try and start up a smart tech AI
committee last year,
and we got a couple of things that we
discussed,
but we didn't really get much traction.
So offhand,
I don't think there's anyone that's
pessimistic. It's more,
I think it's more interest and trying to
Ohh, good, good.
understand, like you said, doing,
and when you mentioned it, I was like,
yeah,
I actually probably could have done
something like that,
like a chat bot for the HR part.
HR policies and stuff like that. Yeah,
I think that's more around, yeah,
instead of trying to think big and go,
well,
what can we really change the world with?
It's, as you say, it's the little wins.
Post.
So,
and I think by showing a couple of those
things, and that's what I'm saying,
I think once you get into it,
the guys will start.
Prompting, and then go, "Ohh, okay,
what about this? What about this?
Exactly. That's what you want.
You don't want a committee.
" And I think it will get, of course,
yeah, 100%.
You want 100 people that are
experimenting.
You want what we call a studio lab,
creative and technical studio lab.
Let people get going.
So with a big IT firm,
what we're setting up is an AI innovation
centre because that's what they want to
call it.
But basically people can go there.
and learn how to in a day do the idea
that they have about their workflow or
the team or the division.
Go and do it.
Don't come to the IT team and say build,
you go and build it yourself.
That's where you're going to end.
So, yeah.
Build it yourself.
Excellent.
Is there anything else that I should know?
Please send me a simple NDA because I
have to give it to my legal agent to
approve.
India is very simple.
I see Rodney hasn't sent it to me yet.
Let me just prompt him again quickly.
Yeah.
I might,
I might actually have one in my documents
somewhere.
Yeah,
just send it to me because I'm not
comfortable getting stuff from you if we
don't have that done.
No, that's fine.
And then also,
I'm getting ahead of myself now,
but start thinking about dates for a
master class,
because we're rapidly filling up.
We're in an unbelievably interesting
situation for ourselves.
But if we start an engagement with you,
I don't want to
everyone excited Monday,
and then all of a sudden I say, well,
the next time you can come in June,
you know?
Yeah, not sure.
So start thinking provisionally when you
can get 12 people in a room or 24 / 4
days so that we can provisionally book it
in.
And once you've decided that that's what
you want to do,
that we actually have the time available.
So, okay, I'll do that.
I'll start trying to get dates. Cool.
Yeah. Awesome.
How many, is it two days or four days?
Well, the standard one is 2 days,
but the technology now is getting so fast
and vast that we also start to consider 2
1/2 days for daily Maverick,
because a lot of people complain and
because they want to send their
colleagues, we say, okay,
you're the one that wants to do it in 2
1/2 days, so don't complain, it's long.
Okay, if you wanted 2 1/2 days,
we can do two. If you wanted three days,
we can do three.
But initially people always say, oh,
you know what, we don't have two days.
Let's do it in half a day.
And then we did it in half a day and
people said, we're lost.
No, 100%, yeah.
We don't know what to do it. Well,
we told you.
You need two days to start to really get
comfortable.
Get into it, yeah.
The first day you're unlearning stuff.
The first day is about unlearning.
The second day is about starting to learn
and then a rocket ship to the moon.
That's the next step.
But then we sometimes see that certain
people still want a little bit of hand
holding.
So what we're now starting to do is that
we have a refresher course after a
quarter. So people come back and say,
I started using it.
This is where I come unstuck.
And then we take them again on a full day
of
rapid learning.
But if you wanted a four-day tailored
program, we could do that as well.
But obviously then we have to do a lot
more work and do research for tailored.
You said, if I've got four days,
that's why I was asking,
Yeah.
is it four days or two days?
No, it is 2 days,
but we say limited to 12 people because
Do this, okay.
we're literally helping people type stuff
in their computers. It's not like do this.
People, yes.
If you don't know, we sit with you,
we do it for you.
Yes, no, sure.
We can't do that for more than 12 people
because it's only the two of us.
Yes, no, sure, 100%. No, that's fine.
I will, yeah, I, yeah,
Yeah.
because I think the idea,
so in the initial discussion we had,
the idea would be probably the XCO and
what we call our GMs or our branch
managers. So there's about,
there's five of them, 7.
Okay.
Yeah, so we'd probably just start over 12,
but then possibly also including my IT
team might also get some benefit,
excuse me, some benefit out of it.
So yeah, maybe 22 days might work better,
but I'll get it. We can.
I'll get an idea of everyone's
availability and I'll.
Just prompt also for sort of the idea of
exactly the number of people we'd be
looking at having.
Yeah, and then once we agree a date,
it needs to be a fixed date,
because some other companies said, Jar,
we're having trouble getting people
together. Can we move it out by a week?
I said, no, it's booked, but also, yeah,
But, yeah, no, 100%, no, no, agreed.
this is our bread and butter.
If we can't train, we're not making money,
Hundred percent.
you know? Okay.
100%.
Good.
Splendid.
Carl, thank you very much.
I'm working on this over the weekend,
so please don't hesitate to call me
Saturday, Sunday, day and night.
I'll answer the phone.
I want it to be good on Monday.
Not a problem.
So if you have an idea or a question,
you can call me anytime.
This afternoon I'm travelling,
so I might not be available because I'm
Oh, sure. 100%. Yeah,
otherwise I'll just message you.
in the air.
Okay, great.
And likewise, if you've got any queries,
questions, want some info,
Perfect.
just give me a shot.
It's month end this weekend,
so also pretty much working.
I understand it. Okay. Thanks.
Have a lovely day. We'll speak soon.
Cool. Spend it. Thank you, JJ. Bye.
Thank you. Bye.